(Penny:)Uh, denial. See, sweetie,
the list goes on and on.
(Leonard:)That's just crazy.
(Leonard:)How would my going in there
even help you?
(Penny:)I don't know. You could talk to
her, and maybe if it comes up,
(Penny:)you could ask if she's heard
about the drug.
(Leonard:)What if I get caught?
Fear of failure!
Lack of confidence!
Kind of a wuss!
(Leonard:)Fine, I'll do it.
(Leonard:)But not because of them,
because I love you.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Raj:)Pushover.
Spineless.
(Sheldon:)Still hasn't bought milk
(Sheldon:)even though I told him
two days ago!
(Howard:)That was incredible.
(Bernadette:)It was.
(Bernadette:)I just wish Stuart
wasn't around
(Bernadette:)so we didn't have
to be so quiet.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Howard:)It's not like
he returns the favor
(Howard:)when he watches
his Japanese porn cartoons.
(knocking)
STUART: You guys got a minute,
(Stuart(knocking):)or are you
still cuddling?
(mouthing)
(Howard:)What is it, Stuart?
STUART:
Can I come in?
(Howard:)Hang on.
(quietly):
Should I send him away?
(Bernadette:)No, it's okay.
STUART:
Thanks, Bernie.